Hello guys, in today's video we are going to talk
about II Lord General Insurance, which disclosed its quarterly numbers during today's trading session.
All the terms are in lex, so do
not get confused at all, I will
convert them into crores and tell you, then
after that we are going to do a very good chart analysis,
so do stay tuned till the end of the video.
So when you see the total revenue of the company, the
total revenue
posted by the company is around Rs 5882 crore,
which is around Rs 54 crore in the same quarter last year.
If you
look at it, you will see that the
company has increased its revenue by around 17 to 18 percent if you look at it on a quarterly
basis, year on year basis,
which is a very good thing. Then if you look at it on a
quarterly basis,
you will get to see the same as usual results,
whereas when you look at the
total expenses of the company, you will
get to see that the company has increased its revenue by approximately Rs 5882 crore in this period.
Total expenses are around ₹5 crore 197 crore,
which
was around ₹4000 588 crore in the same quarter last year.
So, somewhere or the other, the expenses
of the company have also increased and
if you look at it on a quarter-on-quarter basis,
you will get to see the same as usual.
When you look at the total profits of the company,
you will get to see the total profit posted by the company,
which came to around ₹724 crore,
which was
around ₹431 crore in the last corresponding period. So, if you see, the
company has shown a very good increase in
its profitability on a year-on-year basis,
which if we talk in percentage terms,
you will get to see an
increase of around 70% on a
year-on-year basis, which is a very good
thing. Along with this, the company has
also decided to give dividend, interim dividend,
which is a company dividend of around ₹100 crore.  It is
going to give an increase of
around ₹ which was given last year within the same quarter. So the
company has increased its profitability somewhere and has
also increased the interim dividend.
Now let's do chart
analysis. So, when you look at the chart of ICICI Lord,
you will see that the
company has taken very good support
around an area which is around 82.
If you see, the stock has also crossed the 200 day
moving average somewhere
and it can show a very good
long rally.
If I talk about which price,
around 2275, if this area is
breached, then the trend of this stock which is
currently going negative, this lower low, lower
high which is being formed, will be a break off
structure, then after it will come
inside the trend, so as soon as it comes inside the up trend, then
break out, then retest and
go for long. So, this could be the price action for
this stock. If you watch for 4 hours,
you will see that the
stock has also formed an advance bottom type
formation.  It has been shown and if you
look at it carefully then you can get to see
this guy, so this is one and
if you look at it from every time frame then
you will also get to see this, so a
very good price structure is formed
in the current condition and
in the coming time it can show you targets up to 2200, so
note down these levels and targets, if
anyone asks by commenting then if you like the video then
definitely like it, that's all for today's video,
thank you.